- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- All right, Krusty crew,
listen up.
- 好吧，Krusty 船员，
听着。
Last night's buy one
get one full price
昨晚买了一个
获得一份全价
Krabby Patty sale went great!
蟹黄饼促销非常顺利！
But the crowds left me
restaurant dirtier than usual.
但人群却离我而去
餐厅比平时更脏。
Mm.
毫米。
- Hey.
- 嘿。
- Eeeh.
- 呃。
So I'm gonna need you
所以我需要你
to clean until
this whole place sparkles!
清洁直到
这整个地方都闪闪发光！
- Ooh, you've got it, Mr. K.
- 哦，你明白了，K 先生。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Ooh.
哦。
- Hey.
- 嘿。
- Ugh.
- 呃。
[gasps]
[喘气]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
- SpongeBob, are you
all done cleaning?
- 海绵宝宝，你是吗
都打扫完了吗？
- Oh, just finishing up now,
Mr. Krabs.
- 哦，现在刚刚结束，
蟹老板。
- This place looks great!
- 这个地方看起来很棒！
Well done, lad.
干得好，小伙子。
All right, time
to get back to cooking.
好吧，时间到了
回去做饭。
Huh?
啊？
Oh, where's the grill?
哦，烤架在哪里？
- Oh, I took it outside
to air dry.
- 哦，我把它带到外面了
风干。
See?
看？
- Hmm.
- 唔。
See what?
看到什么？
- The grill.
It's right here.
- 烧烤架。
就在这里。
- Right here where?
- 就在这里哪里？
- Under my arm, silly.
- 在我胳膊下，傻瓜。
- The grill is gone.
- 烤架不见了。
- [laughs]
The grill is gone.
- [笑]
烤架不见了。
The grill is gone!
烤架没了！
[screams]
The grill is gone!
[尖叫声]
烤架没了！
The grill is gone!
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[breathing heavily]
[呼吸粗重]
Grill gone.
烧烤架不见了。
The grill gone.
烤架不见了。
Oh, look, it must be
the grill's trail.
哦，你看，一定是
烧烤架的踪迹。
Ah.
啊。
There's still
some grease flavor here.
还有
这里有些油脂味。
Come on, Mr. Krabs,
来吧，蟹老板，
I'll taste the trail
all the way to the grill.
我会品尝那条路
一直到烤架。
- Um, we could
just use our eyes, boyo.
- 嗯，我们可以
只要用我们的眼睛，男孩。
- Oh, great idea,
Mr. Krabs.
-哦，好主意，
蟹老板。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Look, Mr. Krabs,
a race boat garage.
- 看，蟹老板先生，
赛艇车库。
But what would a garage
need a grill for?
但车库会怎样
需要烤架吗？
Huh?
Hmm.
啊？
唔。
- This ain't
no garage.
- 这不是
没有车库。
This here's a clubhouse
这是一个俱乐部会所
for local ragamuffins,
urchins, and waifs.
对于当地的衣衫褴褛的人来说，
海胆和流浪儿。
Look, and there's me grill.
看，这就是我的烧烤炉。
- What are they doing
to it, Mr. Krabs?
- 他们在做什么
螃蟹先生？
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
- Cool.
- 凉爽的。
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
- Whoop.
- 哎呀。
- Ah, no!
- 啊，不！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Why, why?
- 为什么，为什么？
[drill whirs]
[钻头呼呼地响]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- No, not
the cooking surface!
- 不，不
烹饪表面！
That's where
all the flavor is!
那就是那里
所有的味道都是！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- SpongeBob, zip it.
- 海绵宝宝，拉上拉链。
- Ooh, thanks.
- 哦，谢谢。
You know, not every friend'll
tell you when you--
你知道，不是每个朋友都会
告诉你，当你——
- You stay here.
- 你留在这里。
I'm gonna get
me grill back.
我会得到
我烤回来。
- But how, Mr. Krabs?
- 但是怎么样呢，蟹老板？
- Don't worry, boyo,
they're just kids.
- 别担心，男孩，
他们只是孩子。
They have
to listen to me.
他们有
听我说。
Hello, children.
哈喽，孩子们。
I'm an adult.
我是成年人了。
This here is me grill,
这是我的烧烤架，
so I'll just be
taking it back now.
所以我就这样
现在把它收回来。
- Hey, what do you think
you're doing, mister?
- 嘿，你觉得怎么样
你在做什么，先生？
That's our racing cart.
这就是我们的赛车。
- Racing cart?
- 赛车？
That's no "racing cart."
那不是“赛车”。
That there is a top-of-the-line
Grill King 3000,
有一个顶级的
烧烤王3000，
and it belongs to me.
它属于我。
See? I brought all
the relevant paperwork.
看？我全都带来了
相关文件。
- This looks like homework.
- 这看起来像家庭作业。
We don't take kindly
to homework around here.
我们不善待
在这里做作业。
- Yeah.
- 是的。
- Homework stinks.
- 作业很臭。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- I think you just wanna
steal our racing cart.
- 我想你只是想
偷我们的赛车。
- I can't steal
something I already own.
- 我不能偷东西
我已经拥有的东西。
[groans]
[呻吟]
That's it.
Out of me way, you imps.
就是这样。
别挡我的路，你这个小鬼。
Grown up coming through.
长大了就过去了。
- Hold your sea horses,
old man.
- 握住你的海马，
老头儿。
[clicks tongue]
[咔嚓舌头]
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
[sea horse whinnies]
[海马嘶嘶声]
- [snarls]
- [咆哮]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Heh, that's it?
呵呵，就这样吧？
Your little kiddie
trap doesn't--
你的小宝贝
陷阱不——
Ah!
啊!
[laughter]
[笑声]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
Mr. Krabs, you okay?
蟹老板，你还好吗？
- [gibberish]
- [胡言乱语]
- Let me try talking
to them, Mr. Krabs.
- 让我试着说话
对他们来说，蟹老板。
I think
I can reach them.
我认为
我可以联系到他们。
After all,
I have something you don't:
毕竟，
我有你没有的东西：
the heart of a child.
一颗孩子的心。
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
- [sniffs]
- [嗅嗅]
Yeah, not a bad little cart
you guys have built.
是啊，不错的小推车
你们已经建造了。
- Oh, gee, mister,
you think so?
- 噢，天啊，先生，
你这么认为吗？
- Mm-hmm, too bad
it looks so slow.
- 嗯嗯，太糟糕了
看起来好慢。
all: Huh?
全体：啊？
- Yep, no way this thing
could beat our cart,
- 是的，这件事不可能
可以打败我们的购物车，
not in a million years.
一百万年内不会。
- Our cart is the fastest
in Bikini Bottom.
- 我们的购物车是最快的
在比基尼底部。
both: The fastest!
两人：最快！
- Oh, really?
- 哦真的吗？
If only there was
some way to prove it.
如果有的话
某种方式来证明这一点。
- How's about
a race, then?
- 怎么样
那么比赛呢？
- How's about the winner
of the race
- 获胜者怎么样
比赛的
gets to keep
the loser's racing cart?
得到保留
失败者的赛车？
- How's about it's on?
- 开着怎么样？
See you tomorrow morning
at the top of Murder Hill.
明天早上见
在谋杀山顶。
- What do you think
you're doing, boyo?
- 你觉得怎么样
你在做什么，男孩？
We don't have a racing cart.
我们没有赛车。
- Of course we do,
Mr. Krabs.
- 我们当然知道，
蟹老板。
There's just some
assembly required.
只是有一些
需要组装。
Oh!
哦！
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- You sure we built
this thing right?
- 你确定我们建造了
这件事对吗？
It looks a little funky.
它看起来有点时髦。
- Well, what do you mean?
- 嗯，你什么意思？
We followed my blueprint.
我们遵循我的蓝图。
Besides, there's nothing
to worry about.
除此之外，什么也没有
担心。
We just have to make it
through one quick race
我们只需要做到
通过一场快速比赛
down a teensy weensy little
下来一个很小的小
deadly, steep, utterly
terrifying hill.
致命的、陡峭的、完全的
可怕的山。
[gasps]
[喘气]
[pterodactyls caw]
[翼手龙的叫声]
[gulps]
[吞咽]
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Ha, you call that
a racing cart?
- 哈，你管这个叫
赛车？
Looks more like the slow boat
to Palookaville.
看起来更像是慢船
到帕卢卡维尔。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- It's on,
you whippersnappers.
- 已开启，
你们这些自命不凡的人。
Plankton,
what are you doing here?
浮游生物，
你在这里做什么？
- When I heard your grill
was on the line,
- 当我听到你的烧烤声时
正在上线，
I had to get in on this race.
我必须参加这场比赛。
If there's even one little
smudge of patty on there,
如果哪怕有一点点
那里有肉饼的污迹，
the formula will be mine.
公式将是我的。
[chuckles]
[笑声]
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- [growls]
- [咆哮]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Barnacles.
藤壶。
- Whoa!
- 哇！
- Ah, huh?
- 啊，啊？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
- Oh.
- 哦。
- Haha, take that!
- 哈哈，拿走吧！
- Watch it, you hooligan!
- 小心点，你这个流氓！
- [laughs]
- [groans]
- [笑]
- [呻吟]
SpongeBob, look out!
海绵宝宝，小心！
- Ah, whoa, yeow!
- 啊，哇，哟！
[loud crash]
[巨响]
[all laugh]
[全都笑]
- Mr. Krabs,
the steering's out.
- 蟹老板先生，
方向盘坏了。
They cut our brakes.
他们切断了我们的刹车。
What do we do?
我们该怎么办？
- Uh, oh, uh, maybe
we should call their parents?
- 呃，哦，呃，也许
我们应该打电话给他们的父母吗？
- No, Mr. Krabs.
- 不，蟹老板。
You can't win a kids' game
by thinking like an adult.
你不可能赢得儿童游戏
像成年人一样思考。
You have to think young.
你必须年轻地思考。
- You're right, boyo.
- 你是对的，男孩。
We have to delve deep
back into me childhood.
我们必须深入研究
回到我的童年。
[crying]
[哭泣]
- Too far back, Mr. Krabs.
Too far.
- 太落后了，蟹老板。
太远了。
- Oh, oh, oh,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 哦，哦，哦，
是啊，是啊，是啊，是啊。
Check this out.
看看这个。
I learned it in me old
Wormtown skating days.
我在老的时候就学会了
沃姆敦滑冰日。
- Whoa, Mr. Krabs,
I didn't know you could shred.
- 哇哦，蟹老板先生，
我不知道你能撕碎。
- Whoo, hey.
- 呼，嘿。
I got a plan!
Hold on!
我有一个计划！
坚持，稍等！
Plug 'em in, boyo.
把它们插上，男孩。
- Oh.
- 哦。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Come on, SpongeBob.
- 来吧，海绵宝宝。
What's the holdup?
有什么阻碍？
- Sorry, Mr. Krabs.
- 对不起，蟹老板。
My hands get clammy
when I'm defying death.
我的手变得湿冷
当我反抗死亡的时候。
See?
看？
♪ Ta-da ♪
♪ 达达 ♪
[laughs]
[笑]
- Enough magic tricks.
- 足够的魔术。
Plug 'em in!
插入它们！
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- Yeah!
- 是的！
[sizzling]
[嘶嘶声]
all: Oh, oh, ow, ow, ow!
全体：哦哦哦哦哦哦！
Whoa!
哇！
Oh.
哦。
- Ah.
- 啊。
Huh?
啊？
Mmm.
嗯。
- Yay, the finish line!
- 耶，终点线！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Huh? Ugh.
啊？啊。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[loud crash]
[巨响]
[shudders]
I won.
[颤抖]
我赢了。
And so after some quick
thinking and fancy racerin',
所以经过一些快速的
思考和幻想赛车，
I won me grill back.
我把烧烤赢回来了。
I looked those kids
in the eye and said,
我看着那些孩子
看着他的眼睛说道：
"I own these streets.
“我拥有这些街道。
"Don't come back to me
restaurant ever again...
“别回到我身边
餐厅再次...
Until you have money."
直到你有钱为止。”
Adults rule!
大人统治！
[laughs]
[笑]
[laughter]
[笑声]
[loud crashing]
[巨响]
Hey, what's going on?
嘿，发生什么事了？
- Whoa, let's see 'em
beat us this time.
- 哇，让我们看看他们
这次打败了我们。
[whistles]
[口哨声]
[all grunting]
[全都咕哝]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Here we go cart again!
- 我们又来推车了！
[laughs]
[笑]
- Zip it, boyo.
- 拉上拉链，男孩。
- Oh, thanks, Mr. Krabs.
- 哦，谢谢，蟹老板。
Not everybody'll
tell you when--
不是每个人都会
告诉你什么时候——
[mysterious music]
[神秘的音乐]
♪ ♪
[people cheering]
[人们欢呼]
- Beat it, we're closed!
- 别这样，我们关门了！
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
Whoa, there
is nothing better
哇，那里
没有什么比这更好的了
than spending 18 hours
at Glove World,
比花18小时
在手套世界，
even if my feet
are a bit tired.
即使我的脚
有点累了。
- [snoring]
- [打鼾]
- Mine are hungry.
- 我的饿了。
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
Too bad the Krusty Krab
doesn't stay open this late.
可惜了蟹堡王
这么晚都不开门。
- Of course it does!
- 当然可以！
See?
看？
- Huh?
- 啊？
Mr. Krabs never mentioned
we had a night shift.
蟹老板从未提及
我们上夜班。
Huh?
啊？
all: Patrick!
全体：帕特里克！
- Hi, guys!
- 嗨，大家好！
- You sure are popular.
- 你确实很受欢迎。
- I come here
every night.
- 我来这里
每个晚上。
- Blech.
- 布莱赫。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
- [belches]
- [打嗝]
Hi, Patrick.
嗨，帕特里克。
- Long time
no see, man.
- 很长时间
没看见，伙计。
- Hi, Jennifer.
Hi, Chuck.
- 嗨，詹妮弗。
嗨，查克。
- [slurps]
- [啜饮]
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
Oh, oh!
哦，哦！
- Good evening.
- 晚上好。
- Whoa.
- 哇哦。
- Amuse-bouche,
sir?
- 开胃小菜，
先生？
Isopod fillets sprinkled with
polyps on a bed of seagrass,
等足类鱼片撒上
海草床上的息肉，
drizzled with coral slime
and just a soupçon of algae.
淋上珊瑚粘液
和一碗藻类汤。
[pops]
[流行音乐]
- Don't mind if I do.
- 如果我这样做的话，请不要介意。
Mmm.
嗯。
Mmm, mmm, not bad.
嗯嗯，还不错。
[passes gas]
- Eee.
[放气]
- 呃。
- Pardon me.
- 请原谅我。
- Oh, hey.
- 哦，嘿。
- Sorry, buddy.
- 对不起，伙计。
- The night shift certainly
attracts a different crowd.
- 当然是夜班
吸引了不同的人群。
- Come over here,
SpongeBob.
- 过来这里，
海绵宝宝。
I want you
to meet someone.
我想要你
去见某人。
SpongeBob,
this is Squidabeth.
海绵宝宝，
这是斯奎达贝斯。
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Good to meet you,
Mr. Bob.
- 很高兴认识你，
鲍勃先生。
- Oh, a pleasure,
mademoiselle.
- 哦，很高兴，
小姐。
- [giggles]
Ain't you a little charmer?
- [咯咯笑]
你是不是一个小魅力？
- [laughs]
Yeah, I am.
- [笑]
是的，我是。
- What you fixin' to have,
honey child?
- 你想要什么，
亲爱的孩子？
- One Krabby Patty, please.
- 请来一份蟹肉饼。
- A Krabby what?
- 蟹蟹什么？
We ain't got
none of those, hon.
我们没有
这些都不是，亲爱的。
- You don't serve
Krabby Patties?
- 你不服务
蟹肉饼？
- But we got lots
of other tasty vittles.
- 但我们有很多
其他美味的食物。
- "Howling rings,
sucker shakes,
-“嚎叫声响起，
吸盘摇晃，
boo-gers, crawly fries"?
鼻屎、爬行薯条”？
- Give us the works!
- 给我们作品！
- One great Pacific
garbage patch!
- 一个伟大的太平洋
垃圾补丁！
- Order up!
- 订购吧！
- Oh, boy, oh, boy,
oh, boy.
- 哦，男孩，哦，男孩，
哦，男孩。
You gotta try
a sucker shake.
你必须尝试
摇晃得很厉害。
[slurping]
[发出声音]
Ah, drink up, buddy.
啊，喝点酒吧，伙计。
- I'm--
[babbles]
- 我是--
[胡言乱语]
- Yum.
- 嗯。
- [grumbling]
- [抱怨]
- The howling rings
are a scream.
- 嚎叫声
是一声尖叫。
- [howls]
- [嚎叫]
[both howling]
[两人都嚎叫]
- A little different,
but I like it.
- 有点不同，
但我喜欢它。
Give the chef
my compliments.
给厨师
我的赞美。
- Why, tell him
yourself, sweetie.
- 为什么，告诉他
你自己，亲爱的。
You got a visitor!
有客人来了！
- Come on back!
- 回来吧！
Hey there, night feeders.
嘿，夜间喂食者。
Name's Barry Blobfish.
我的名字是巴里·水滴鱼。
Good to know ya.
很高兴认识你。
- Good to meet you, Barry.
- 很高兴认识你，巴里。
I'm SpongeBob.
我是海绵宝宝。
- Yikes!
- 哎呀！
Oh, that's
my cooking hand.
哦，那是
我的做饭手。
- Oh, sorry.
- 哦，抱歉。
Used my spatula arm.
用了我的抹刀臂。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[loud rumbling]
[巨响]
- Night train!
- 夜行列车！
[train whistle blows]
[火车鸣笛]
- Oh, no,
the midnight rush.
- 哦，不，
午夜高峰。
What am I gonna do?
我要做什么？
Oh, if only there was
a fry cook in the house.
哦，如果有的话就好了
家里有一个炒菜的厨师。
- Oh, I'm a certified
fry cook!
- 哦，我是经过认证的
炒菜做饭！
- Oh, let's see.
- 哦，让我们看看。
I'd have to clear it
with the night manager.
我必须清除它
和夜班经理。
Hey, boss,
can this little fella here
嘿，老板，
这个小家伙可以在这里吗
take over
my shift tonight?
接管
今晚我值班吗？
[creepy music]
[令人毛骨悚然的音乐]
[evil laugh]
[邪恶的笑声]
- Nosferatu?
- 诺斯费拉图？
Oh.
哦。
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
- [sniffs]
- [嗅嗅]
[slurps]
[啜饮]
[belches]
[打嗝]
- You got the job, kid.
- 你得到了这份工作，孩子。
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
- Whew.
- 呼。
Now I can pass out
in peace.
现在我可以昏倒了
平静地。
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Invisible Stan,
let's get him to a hospital.
- 隐形斯坦，
我们送他去医院吧。
Wounded fry cook
coming through!
受伤的炒菜厨师
来了！
- Hey, get
your grill in gear.
- 嘿，得到
你的烤架已启动。
The crowd's getting restless.
人群变得焦躁起来。
- Uh, yes, ma'am.
- 呃，是的，女士。
Oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah.
哦，哦，哦，哦，是的。
They are gonna
love this.
他们要
喜欢这个。
[all grumbling]
[大家都在抱怨]
Here, try a sample
from the daytime menu.
在这里，尝试一下示例
从白天的菜单中。
Whee, whoa.
哇哦。
- [chomping]
- [咀嚼]
[all eating noisily]
[大家都吵吵嚷嚷地吃东西]
- Bleh.
- 布莱赫。
- Blah.
- 废话。
- [gags]
- [笑声]
Bleh.
布莱赫。
- Bleh.
- 布莱赫。
[all vomiting]
[全都呕吐]
- What the devilfish
did you make?
- 什么魔鬼鱼
你做了吗？
- Well, Krabby Patties,
of course.
- 好吧，蟹肉饼，
当然。
- [gags]
- [笑声]
You tryin' to poison us?
你想毒害我们吗？
Quit fooling around
and cook up something edible.
别再胡闹了
并煮一些可以吃的东西。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Whoa.
哇哦。
That's impossible.
那是不可能的。
Everyone loves
Krabby Patties.
每个人都喜欢
蟹肉饼。
What kind of a weird
upside-down place is this?
什么样的怪异
这是颠倒的地方吗？
- And no more
of that daytime slop!
- 不再有
那个白天的泥水！
- Krabby Patties aren't slop.
- 蟹黄饼不潦草。
Got to be something
they like in here.
必须是某种东西
他们喜欢在这里。
No.
不。
[sniffs]
[嗅嗅]
Huh?
啊？
Oh, no!
哦，不！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
- Oh, now, lookie here.
- 哦，现在，看这里。
Night patties!
晚上吃肉饼！
Now you're getting
the swing of it.
现在你得到了
它的摆动。
- N-N-Night patties?
- N-N-Night 肉饼？
- Order up, people!
- 订购吧，人们！
- All right,
night patties.
- 好吧，
晚上肉饼。
- Tasty.
- 好吃。
- [chomping]
- [咀嚼]
[ghosts whimper]
[鬼魂呜咽]
Smooth.
光滑的。
[ghost whimpers]
[幽灵呜咽]
- Ah.
- 啊。
[ghosts whimper]
[鬼魂呜咽]
Smoky.
烟。
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
- Yeah!
- 是的！
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
- Everybody down
on the floor.
- 大家都下来
在地板上。
- It's the Fisherman!
- 这是渔夫！
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
both: No,
not the Fisherman!
两者：不，
不是渔夫！
- Now hand over the moola.
- 现在交出钱。
[all whimpering]
[全都呜咽]
[cash register dings]
[收银机叮叮声]
- Well, good evening, sir.
- 嗯，晚上好，先生。
Welcome to
the Krusty Krab.
欢迎来到
蟹堡王。
- Give me all your money!
- 把你所有的钱都给我！
- Well, always glad to help
a fellow out with a loan.
- 嗯，总是很乐意提供帮助
一个借钱出去的人
- Loan?
I don't want a loan.
- 贷款？
我不想贷款。
I'm the Fisherman.
我是渔夫。
I'm robbing the place.
我要抢地方了
- Well, that
is downright unfriendly.
- 嗯，那个
是彻头彻尾的不友好。
I'm putting you under
fry cook's arrest.
我把你放在下面
弗莱厨师被捕。
- Huh?
- 啊？
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
[laughs]
[笑]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Ooh, oh!
哦哦！
Ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeek!
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊！
[groaning]
[呻吟]
- I got you now.
- 我现在找到你了。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
Not so fast.
没那么快。
- Whoa, uh.
- 哇，呃。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
Yee ah!
呀呀！
Waa!
哇！
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Wha, oh!
哇哦！
- Well, looks like the hook
is on the other fin now, huh?
- 嗯，看起来像钩子
现在在另一个鳍上，是吧？
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Don't worry, my friends.
- 别担心，我的朋友们。
I have captured
the evil doer.
我已捕获
恶人。
- Hey, leave him alone!
- 嘿，别管他了！
- Just what do you
think you're doing?
- 你到底要做什么
你觉得你在做什么？
- Uh, catching a criminal.
- 呃，抓罪犯。
- He's no criminal.
- 他不是罪犯。
He works here.
他在这里工作。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- He robs us every night.
- 他每晚都会抢劫我们。
- It's a night shift
tradition.
- 这是夜班
传统。
- Oh, a night shift tradition.
- 哦，夜班传统。
[clears throat]
Heh, heh, oops.
[清嗓子]
嘿嘿嘿，哎呀。
Sorry about that,
Mr. Fisherman, sir.
对此感到抱歉，
渔夫先生，先生。
Oy.
哎哟。
- No worries,
little yellow thing.
- 不用担心，
黄色的小东西。
You got some
mean fishing skills.
你有一些
意思是钓鱼技巧。
Respect.
尊重。
- Oh.
[giggles]
- 哦。
[咯咯笑]
You're not so bad
yourself.
你没那么坏
你自己。
Oh, yow!
哦，哟！
- Attention,
- 注意力，
let's welcome our newest member
of the night shift.
让我们欢迎我们的最新成员
夜班的。
What's your name again?
你又叫什么名字？
- [whispers]
SpongeBob SquarePants.
- [低语]
海绵宝宝。
- SquareBob SpongePants.
- SquareBob 海绵裤。
- Okay, close enough.
- 好吧，足够接近了。
- A round of night patties
for everyone!
- 一轮夜间肉饼
对于每个人！
I'm buying!
我买！
[all cheer]
[大家欢呼]
[foghorn blares]
[雾号声]
- Quittin' time!
- 下班时间到了！
- Oh, already?
- 哦，已经？
- I'm back.
- 我回来了。
- Barry!
- 巴里！
- Thanks for helping out,
SpongeBob.
- 感谢您的帮助，
海绵宝宝。
- Oh, it was nothing.
- 哦，没什么。
Oh, I'm gonna
miss you guys.
哦，我要
想念你们。
[all laugh]
[全都笑]
- Come and visit us
again soon, honey.
- 来拜访我们
很快就会再来一次，亲爱的。
- We're here
every night.
- 我们在这里
每个晚上。
- Huh, huh, huh?
- 哈，哈，哈？
- What are you doing here
so early, boyo?
- 你在这里做什么
这么早啊，小子？
- Oh, I was helping out
on the night shift.
-哦，我正在帮忙
上夜班。
- Night shift, hmm?
- 夜班，嗯？
We don't have
a night shift.
我们没有
夜班。
Hmm, must have been
a bad dream, kiddo.
嗯，一定是
一个噩梦，孩子。
- Huh?
- 啊？
Gee, guess I must
have been sleep-working.
哎呀，我想我必须
一直在睡觉工作。
- Well, I ain't
sleep-paying you,
- 嗯，我不是
睡眠支付你，
so get to wakey-working.
所以开始清醒工作吧。
- Yes, sir.
- 是的，先生。
[sighs]
[叹气]
Yow!
哟！
A fish hook?
鱼钩？
- Case history of a fry cook
who wanted a late night snack
- 一位油炸厨师的案例
谁想吃夜宵
but ended up
in the fry vat of doubt.
但最终
在怀疑的鱼缸里。
Mr. SquarePants
will never know
方裤先生
永远不会知道
he has worked a shift
in "The Tidal Zone."
他轮班了
在《潮汐区》中。
[train whistle blows]
[火车鸣笛]
- I'd like five night patties
to go, please.
- 我想要五个夜间肉饼
请走吧。